{
  "apikey": "%PUT-YOUR-API-KEY-HERE%",
  "description": "This is simple calibration data used for testing purposes. Do not use it in production environment!",
  "copyright": "Copyright (C) 2238 by BanAN Technologies Inc.",
  "test-data": [
    {
      "question": "32 + 45",
      "answer": 77
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 96",
      "answer": 179
    },
    {
      "question": "41 + 32",
      "answer": 73
    },
    {
      "question": "90 + 12",
      "answer": 102
    },
    {
      "question": "23 + 6",
      "answer": 29
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 61",
      "answer": 65
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 30",
      "answer": 69
    },
    {
      "question": "63 + 2",
      "answer": 65
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 55",
      "answer": 135
    },
    {
      "question": "90 + 87",
      "answer": 177
    },
    {
      "question": "77 + 43",
      "answer": 120
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 15",
      "answer": 48
    },
    {
      "question": "100 + 76",
      "answer": 176
    },
    {
      "question": "64 + 4",
      "answer": 68
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 11",
      "answer": 68
    },
    {
      "question": "30 + 49",
      "answer": 79
    },
    {
      "question": "25 + 50",
      "answer": 75
    },
    {
      "question": "34 + 2",
      "answer": 36
    },
    {
      "question": "68 + 99",
      "answer": 167
    },
    {
      "question": "78 + 63",
      "answer": 141
    },
    {
      "question": "34 + 71",
      "answer": 105
    },
    {
      "question": "22 + 12",
      "answer": 34
    },
    {
      "question": "11 + 3",
      "answer": 14
    },
    {
      "question": "26 + 34",
      "answer": 60
    },
    {
      "question": "82 + 38",
      "answer": 120
    },
    {
      "question": "36 + 63",
      "answer": 99
    },
    {
      "question": "67 + 13",
      "answer": 80
    },
    {
      "question": "64 + 5",
      "answer": 69
    },
    {
      "question": "74 + 60",
      "answer": 134
    },
    {
      "question": "59 + 31",
      "answer": 90
    },
    {
      "question": "50 + 22",
      "answer": 72
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 35",
      "answer": 47
    },
    {
      "question": "97 + 96",
      "answer": 193
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 47",
      "answer": 56
    },
    {
      "question": "93 + 61",
      "answer": 154
    },
    {
      "question": "59 + 88",
      "answer": 147
    },
    {
      "question": "85 + 37",
      "answer": 122
    },
    {
      "question": "32 + 94",
      "answer": 126
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 6",
      "answer": 18
    },
    {
      "question": "20 + 37",
      "answer": 57
    },
    {
      "question": "26 + 93",
      "answer": 119
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 88",
      "answer": 98
    },
    {
      "question": "53 + 8",
      "answer": 61
    },
    {
      "question": "72 + 6",
      "answer": 78
    },
    {
      "question": "58 + 76",
      "answer": 134
    },
    {
      "question": "53 + 58",
      "answer": 111
    },
    {
      "question": "44 + 55",
      "answer": 99
    },
    {
      "question": "63 + 58",
      "answer": 121
    },
    {
      "question": "92 + 36",
      "answer": 128
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 56",
      "answer": 62
    },
    {
      "question": "59 + 67",
      "answer": 126
    },
    {
      "question": "52 + 68",
      "answer": 120
    },
    {
      "question": "99 + 49",
      "answer": 148
    },
    {
      "question": "62 + 46",
      "answer": 108
    },
    {
      "question": "49 + 55",
      "answer": 104
    },
    {
      "question": "38 + 30",
      "answer": 68
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 79",
      "answer": 98
    },
    {
      "question": "31 + 84",
      "answer": 115
    },
    {
      "question": "97 + 41",
      "answer": 138
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 84",
      "answer": 90
    },
    {
      "question": "68 + 6",
      "answer": 74
    },
    {
      "question": "25 + 70",
      "answer": 95
    },
    {
      "question": "40 + 85",
      "answer": 125
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 81",
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "question": "96 + 8",
      "answer": 104
    },
    {
      "question": "38 + 44",
      "answer": 82
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 52",
      "answer": 132
    },
    {
      "question": "16 + 55",
      "answer": 71
    },
    {
      "question": "94 + 73",
      "answer": 167
    },
    {
      "question": "36 + 42",
      "answer": 78
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 58",
      "answer": 67
    },
    {
      "question": "63 + 42",
      "answer": 105
    },
    {
      "question": "35 + 58",
      "answer": 93
    },
    {
      "question": "44 + 86",
      "answer": 130
    },
    {
      "question": "48 + 9",
      "answer": 57
    },
    {
      "question": "100 + 51",
      "answer": 151
    },
    {
      "question": "98 + 77",
      "answer": 175
    },
    {
      "question": "87 + 65",
      "answer": 152
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 54",
      "answer": 87
    },
    {
      "question": "75 + 26",
      "answer": 101
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 46",
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "question": "30 + 90",
      "answer": 120
    },
    {
      "question": "22 + 47",
      "answer": 69
    },
    {
      "question": "58 + 91",
      "answer": 149
    },
    {
      "question": "75 + 67",
      "answer": 142
    },
    {
      "question": "54 + 75",
      "answer": 129
    },
    {
      "question": "72 + 9",
      "answer": 81
    },
    {
      "question": "96 + 62",
      "answer": 158
    },
    {
      "question": "52 + 8",
      "answer": 60
    },
    {
      "question": "68 + 91",
      "answer": 159
    },
    {
      "question": "50 + 98",
      "answer": 148
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 96",
      "answer": 179
    },
    {
      "question": "23 + 19",
      "answer": 42
    },
    {
      "question": "74 + 80",
      "answer": 154
    },
    {
      "question": "62 + 50",
      "answer": 112
    },
    {
      "question": "24 + 52",
      "answer": 76
    },
    {
      "question": "82 + 1",
      "answer": 83
    },
    {
      "question": "24 + 81",
      "answer": 105
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 52",
      "answer": 91
    },
    {
      "question": "93 + 15",
      "answer": 108
    }
  ],
  "chunk": {
    "number": 20,
    "total": 22,
    "size": 100,
    "range": {
      "from": 1900,
      "to": 2000
    }
  }
}